

# **Zeleniuk Dmytro**Software Engineer Front-End

# **CONTACTS**

0	+1 (201) 673-1891
×	dimaszelenyuk@gmail.com
9	New Jersey, USA
in in	https://www.linkedin.com/in /dima-zelenyuk-643943122

# **EDUCATION**

2014-2017 STEP Computer Academy

# PERSONAL INFO

Date of Birth: 11.02.1993 From: Kiev, Ukraine

# **PERSONAL SKILLS**

Responsible Productive

Quick-learner Team player

- Languages: TypeScript, JavaScript, Dart CSS, HTML.
- **Web framework**: Angular, Ionic, Flutter, Phaser 3.
- Build tool: Webpack, Grunt, Gulp, Bower.
- Other: Web3, NgRx, RxJs, Http, Git, Redux, jQuery, MetaMask, D3-charts, Ajax, NPM, Bootstrap, Angular Material, Webflow, FireBase, Google-Cloud, JIRA, Bitbucket Pipelines, Facebook API, Forge, SwaggerGoogle analytics, Intercom, Chatkit, Fondy, Google API, MacOS, Linux, Ubuntu, Windows.
- **IDE**: WebStorm, Visual Studio Code Android Studio, Xcode

## **ABOUT**

I'm a Software Engineer with more than 6 years of commercial experience. Had participated in many interesting and big projects with different domains. During my career I was involved mainly in front-end development, using Angular, Ionic, JavaScript, TypeScript. Had solid experience in integration blockchain smart contracts and work with Web3.

I regard myself as a trustworthy, loyal and dedicated individual and take great pride in my work by paying particular attention to detail.

Equally important, I have experience of mentoring, working in small and large teams of international people, and I consider myself a good teammate.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Capgemini

June 2022 - November 2022

## Senior Angular Developer at Morgan Stanley

- · Project description: Retirement system.
- Responsibilities:
- Building reusable components with service-oriented architects.
- Responsible for code review, refactoring modules to increase productivity of a system.
- Worked in a team, involved in developing the UI layout and front-end programming for web application that matches requirements of Client.
- Responsible for creation unit tests system
- Environment & Tools: Angular 12, Unit tests, JEST, Rest APIs, RxJS, NgRx, Redux, iFrame, Git, Jira, CI/CD, HTML5, SCSS.

## **Applicature**

June 2021 - February 2022

## Lead Frontend Developer at multi tenant Platform.

- · Projects description:
- Platform 1: While designing the projects Ecosystem we recognized the following problems that
  the network marketing,
  cryptocurrency and online shopping industries are struggling with and that can be solved by
  utilizing blockchain technology and a product- advocate-token-based ecosystem.
- Platform 2: aims to be the One-Stop-Shop for GameFi. The platform features a launchpad, a marketplace to trade, lend, and borrow in-game assets, and, along with its roadmap, a community event & tournament system. GameStation allows teams to develop and launch their play-to-earn (P2E) blockchain games while creating a community of like minds focused on participating in developing their favorite games. Gamers, on their side, can access private sales of their favorite games and organize events and compete against other players.
- · Responsibilities:
- Building reusable components with service-oriented architects.
- Responsible for quality of a product, productivity of other developers, code review, refactoring modules to increase productivity of a system.
- testing.
- Environment & Tools: Angular 12, Web3, Rxjs, NgRx, Mobx, S3, Git, Jira, MetaMask, SmartContract, WalletConnect, Bitbucket Pipelines, HTML5, SCSS.

#### **OGD Solutions**

November 2017 - June 2021

## Senior Frontend Developer at Simplify VMS Project.

· Projects description:

Simplify VMS is transformational, award-winning, secure private-cloud Vendor Management System (VMS). Our solution is built on the newest and most flexible technology stack and brimming with integration and system capabilities that redefine the promise of VMS platforms.

- · Responsibilities:
- Responsible for quality of a product, productivity of other developers, code review, new user-oriented functions, refactoring
- modules to increase productivity of a system.
- optimization of this site for maximum speed and scalability;
- team work of more than 15 people
- integration of graphics, widgets, new modules.
- Environment & Tools: Angular 9, TypeScript, Git GitHub, Rxjs, JIRA, D3-charts, HTML5, SCSS.

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### Senior Frontend Developer at PhotoBash Project.

- Project description: Photobash is quickly becoming the best online resource forRoyalty-Free Photography, Masked Images and 3D Models.
- · Responsibilities:
- creation of project architecture and internment of libraries
- development of new user-oriented functions;
- optimization of this site for maximum speed and scalability;
- Environment & Tools: Angular 9, TypeScript, JavaScript, Stripe, Google Analytics, SweetAlert2, Git, Rxjs, Bootstrap, JIRA, Google Sign-in, Facebook Login, HTML5, SCSS.

#### Senior Frontend Developer at Gigway Project

· Projects description:

Gigway let you create a freelancer profile, get matched with quality gigs, communicate directly with companies and get paid from Gigway. The platform also included online documents signing functionality using 3-d party API.

- · Responsibilities:
- Refactoring mobile app, adding new services (analytics, push notifications, advertising)
- Development of new user-facing features;
- Optimizing this application for maximum speed and scalability;
- Unit testing
- Environment & Tools: Angular 5, Ionic4, JavaScript, Git. Websocket, Rxjs. ChatKit, Assently, Intercom, Mixpanel, Laravel Forge, Nova. Angular Material, Google Sign-in, Facebook Login, HTML5, SCSS.

#### Worked as a Front-End Developer at SoldOut Project.

- Project description: SoldOut is application for easy booking or purchase of concert tickets and more. With a paid payment system, you have the opportunity to choose a place or a fan zone. Implemented a convenient filter and search system.
- · Responsibilities:
- Development of site migration from AngularJs to Angular.
- Environment & Tools: HTML5, SCSS Angular JS, Angular 7, JavaScript, Git, Rxjs, Redux, Payment System, Facebook API, analytics Api, i18n translation, Zone.js, Google Analytics

#### Middle mobile Developer at Palms Project.

- Project description: Palms makes booking sports training easy and affordable. Book football fields, courts, boxing lessons and other sports activities right in the app in a couple of clicks.
- · Responsibilities:
- Internment of libraries
- Development of new functionality for the user;
- Optimization of this site for maximum speed and scalability;
- Integration of calendar and payment systems.
- Testing.
- Environment & Tools: Angular 5, Ionic4, Cordova, Payment, JavaScript, Git. Websocket, Rxjs, Trello, xCode, Google Sign-in, Facebook Login, LinkedIn Login, HTML5, SCSS.

## **Dengo Systems**

October 2016 - November 2017

#### Worked as a Front-End manager site for TimeTracker

- Project description: A personnel management software package that offers proof of performance, time tracking and payroll management software.
- Responsibilities: website development for managing and conducting time tracker analytics program. with the implementation of the calendar and screenshot monitor timer tracker users.
- Environment & Tools: Angular JS (1,6), JavaScript, Git, Fullcalendar.io, Facebook API, analytics Api, i18n translation, Bootstrap, Protractor